[{"answer": "Well, I think it's the nature of what Major League Baseball is alleging here.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Why is A-Rod being singled out for what seems to be special punishment?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, the Yankees really didn't want him around as we know.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Where is their integrity in all of this?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Actually, today, Piers, this is a great day for baseball.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "But why you can't the other sports and the authorities that run them do what is happening in tennis and golf?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "All the above.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What's your take on it?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "And has not been playing that well.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I don't know that we can ever trust again.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "We have to trust again that the next wonder kid is going to be clean?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "And yes, that is true.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Well, you know, once you're into that mindset, anything goes, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, my response to that is, it's been policy that bus drivers do not jump in the middle of a fight.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "For those of you who think you should have intervened and done something to help the boy physically, what is your response?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "OODY: In hindsight, I followed policy.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Do you believe with hindsight you could have done anything else than what you did?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I took it really personal.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "But how do you feel personally about what happened?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, I - I didn't want to move the kid.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What is your reaction to what the police chief said there?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's more on me because I didn't do what people thought I should have done.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Should we be focusing on what these three little barbarians did?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I don't think it's fair, no.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Is that fair that you're getting all the flack when these kids, these thugs, are seen on camera trying to kill this kid?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "I retired, Piers, I retired.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Will you carry on, driving buses in light of what's happened here?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, it was a big straw too.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "This was the final straw for you, was it?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, what you're seeing right now with all these embassy closures, is definitely related to what we saw and what we didn't see in terms of a reaction in Benghazi.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "What are the key takeaways we can look forward to seeing tomorrow?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "In a sense -- depends on who you ask.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Are they basically saying, we have to look like we're doing everything we can?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "We're essentially talking about a CIA mission in Benghazi.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Why was manpower so lacking in Benghazi?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "So, because they didn't understand, they just underestimated the threat?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "URNETT: We -- we absolutely are.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "And we are seeing in real time the -- the very extreme action that the American administration is now taking to try and prevent another Benghazi, aren't we?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "You know, it goes in a few places.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "And -- and in the end, where do you see the culpability?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Very blooming.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Isn't that a nice way to put it?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a good move.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "How important is it, Frank Ochberg, do you think to have this house of horrors torn to pieces for -- for the victims in particular?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Piers, I was right there.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What did you make of -- of her performance and what she said?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Well -- well, I absolutely believe that they can be liberated.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "How realistic is it that these three young women can be liberated in the near future?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "You know, I think the Stockholm syndrome has -- has been overplayed on some levels.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "What is your take on that?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Absolutely, to not let their past define them.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "ORGAN: Dr. Bailey, from -- from all your work with Jaycee Dugard there and many others, what is the -- the best advice you could give these three young women from Cleveland as they try and get back to normality in their lives?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Taking it day by day.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "How are you, first of all?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "No, I have no doubt that he was pursuing a hot story.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Do you have any idea really what may have happened?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Well, he loved -- you know, he loved to always challenge conventional wisdom.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "He was a passionate man, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "No, I mean, absolutely.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "The NSA, Edward Snowden, and even all the chatter now, the intrusions (ph) -- this was right up his -- his wheelhouse?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Well, it made life really exciting.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "I mean, it must be dramatic and occasionally pretty scary and all the other things that go with it?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Well, Michael -- I mean, he was a pretty big believer in radical transparency overall.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "When you look at, as I say, all the current stories and stuff, where do you think Michael would have drawn the line between what should be in the public domain and what shouldn't be, in terms of where you decide what's in the national interest to keep quiet and to publish?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "I'm not really but...", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "You a Yankees fan?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Now, I live in New York.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Because you're a New Yorker, right?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a real testament to his legacy and what he stood for, and you know, how -- what a passionate supporter he was of liberty, of human rights, of freedom, of the right to -- of the right to free speech.", "docId": "130805pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Were you surprised by the -- the incredible outpouring of attention that Michael's death got -- the tributes and accolades that came in (ph)?", "qSentId": 608}]